(Dr Hofstadter:)...and I'm here to help.
(Leonard:)That's so nice.
(Dr Hofstadter:)And we're back to the obvious.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Now, what's up?
(Leonard:)Well, uh...
(Leonard:)Okay, um...
I don't wanna get back with Penny.
(Leonard:)We tried it, it was crazy, it didn't work.
(Leonard:)But I can't deal with the fact
that she slept with my friend, Raj.
(Leonard:)And then I find out
that Raj's sister, Priya...
(Leonard:)...who I've been going out with,
is moving back to lndia.
(Leonard:)So I'm just completely confused
and alone.
l understand.
- Got any advice?
- Yes. Buck up.
(Leonard:)Excuse me,
you're a world-renowned expert...
(Leonard:)...in parenting and child development,
and all you've got is "buck up"?
(Howard:)Sorry.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Buck up, sissy pants.
(Dr Hofstadter:)...my books are available on Amazon.